talkingdotnet.com 2019-11-17

# Privacy Policy

The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Contents of this blog-all texts and images may not be published, rewritten, broadcast or redistributed anywhere without permission.

### Disclaimer

This is a personal blog. All the contents of the blog are my own. The content does not represent the views and opinions of the any of my employers.

The idea is to spread the knowledge. The content of this blog is not intended to cause harm, but if You have any concerns about the contents of this blog, please contact me via e-mail. Disagreeing with the content of the blog does not constitute sufficient ground for you to ask to remove or modify any parts of this blog.

If you own rights to any of the images or articles, and do not wish them to appear on this site, please contact me via e-mail([contact@talkingdotnet.com](mailto:contact@talkingdotnet.com)).

We give utmost priority to our visitors. Your privacy is very important to us. To better protect your privacy we are providing this notice explaining our online information practices so that you can make a better choice while providing your information.

### Personal Information

We may collect personal information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How we use collected information

TalkingDotnet may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To run and operate our Site_  
We may need your information display content on the Site correctly.
  * _To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send them information and updates pertaining to their order.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

TalkingDotnet has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

This document was last updated on August 09, 2016

**PS:** If you found this content valuable and want to return the favour, then [](https://www.buymeacoffee.com/talkingdotnet)
